
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "How many sharps are there in the key of D major?",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
            "1",
            "2",
            "0",
            "4",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which musical notation symbolizes a flat note?",
        answer: "‚ô≠",
        options: [
            "‚ô≠",
            "#",
            "‚ôÆ",
            "none of these",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which one of these is a 16th note?",
        answer: "both 1 and 2",
        options: [
            "ùÖ°",
            "‚ô´",
            "ùÖ†",
            "both 1 and 2",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What scale represents the A minor scale",
        answers: "A-B-C-D-E-F-G-A",
        options: [
            "A-B-C-D-E-F-G-A",
            "A-B-C-D-E-F‚ôØ-G-A",
            "A-B-C‚ôØ-D-E-F‚ôØ-G‚ôØ-A",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "In a given scale what notes make up a major chord",
        answer: "1-3-5, 4-6-8, 5-7-2",
        options: [
            "1-3-5, 4-6-8, 5-7-2",
            "2-4-6, 3,5,7, 6-8-3",
            "None of the Above",
            "All of the Above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "In a given scale what notes make up a minor chord",
        answer: "2-4-6, 3,5,7, 6-8-3",
        options: [
            "1-3-5, 4-6-8, 5-7-2",
            "2-4-6, 3,5,7, 6-8-3",
            "None of the Above",
            "All of the Above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "In a given scale what notes make up a diminsished chord",
        answer: "7-2-4",
        options: [
            "1-3-5, 4-6-8, 5-7-2",
            "2-4-6, 3,5,7, 6-8-3",
            "7-2-4",
            "None of the Above",
            "All of the Above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which one is a quarter rest?",
        answer: "ùÑΩ",
        options: [
            "ùÑæ",
            "ùÑº",
            "ùÑ´",
            "ùÑΩ",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is another way to write 4/4 in the time signature line?",
        answer: "ùÑ¥",
        options: [
            "ùÑµ",
            "ùÑû",
            "ùÑ¥",
            "none",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is another name for the tremle clef ùÑû?",
        answer: "The G Clef",
        options: [
            "The G Clef",
            "The F Clef",
            "The Piano Clef",
            "The Clef chin",
        ]
    },
]